<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>your page's title</title>
 <link href="http://your.pages.url/atom.xml" rel="self" />
 <link href="http://your.pages.url/" />
 <updated>2013-02-28T17:17:40-08:00</updated>
 <id>http://your.pages.url<id>
 <author>
   <name>site.owner-name</name>
   <email>site.owner-email</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>First Post</title>
   <link href="http://your.pages.url/poetry/2012/02/28/first-post.html" />
   <updated>2012-02-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://lebobs.ch//poetry/2012/02/28/first-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id='mushrooms_in_japanese_verse_haiku_collected_by_rh_blyth_various_dates_some_go_back_to_the_17th_century'&gt;Mushrooms in Japanese Verse, haiku collected by R.H. Blyth. Various dates. Some go back to the 17th Century.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming down the mountain Hatsutake no Through the drizzle kaori n furidasu To the scent of the first mushrooms kosame kana Chigetsu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mushroom hunting Nigemo They don&amp;#8217;t run away senu no wo awate But everyone is in such a hurry! kinoko-gari&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretending Kai kinoko The mushrooms bought totta furi shite Had been gathered modori keri Issa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be nice to make Enmao The lord&amp;#8217;s retainer warai kinoko wo Eat Laughing Mushroom chito maire Issa (Gymnopilus spectabilis, Laughing Jim)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking hold with the hand Ureshisa no Of the happiness of the mountain yama wo Tsukamu ya Mushroom gathering! raisha Kinokogari Raisha&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mushroom gathering Takegari ya Only the crescent Moon mikazuki hitotsu Left unplucked sanrei Torinokoshi Sanrei&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The oak tree falls on them Hahaso ochite and the scent rises matsutake mienu of unseen Matsutake gyoji Nioi kana Gyoji&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I forgot falling off the horse Ureshisa ni With the happiness rakuba wasururu Of finding mushrooms ukei Kinoko kana Ukei&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matsutake; Matsutake ya Taken by someone else hito ni toraruru Right in front of my nose kyorai Hana no saki Kyorai&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mushroom gathering: Takegari ya Today let&amp;#8217;s go on until we fall over kyo wa ki no ne ni The roots of the trees kaso Korobu made Kaso&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matsutake Matsutake ya From the depths of the pine forest matsu yori oku no The voice of the hawk taka no koe Koya&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mushroom gathering; Takegari ya From greediness yoku kara michi ni We lost our way fumimayoi Jiraku&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before my hand Te no mae ni Stretched out for the mushroom cho no ikizuku A butterfly breathing kinoko kana Issa&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>